Finding Aid for Frank and Peggy Bach Papers, 1964-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual Materials
  - Photographs
    - Theatre (Box 8)
      (includes University of Michigan Experimental Conference; Kimathi Performance Workshop; The Players Amateur Theatre Club; Mad Madonnas; Marcel Marceau; "The Birds;" "Little Red;" "Louis;" "The Fabulous Miss Marie;" "No Tears for the Ghetto Man;" "Ebenezer is a Geezer;" "Life of a King;" Michigan Repertory Theatre; Detroit Repertory Theatre; University of Michigan Theatre Program; Power Center: "Don't Bother Me I Can't Cope" and the San Francisco Mime Troupe; Court Theatre: "The Fantasticks;" Fisher Theater: "Raisin," "Sherlock Holmes," and "Carnaval Do Brazil;" Theatre Company of Ann Arbor: "Bitch You Crazy;" Oakland University: "Westside Story;" Detroit Youtheatre: "The Revolutionary Mother Goose;" and Music Hall Center: "1776" and "Met Week")
    - Leon Thomas (Box 8)
    - Tribe (Box 8)
    - Two-Five-One (II-V-I) Orchestra (Box 8)
    - The UP (Box 8)
    - The Urbations 1982-1985, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Jimmy Van Dyke 1980 (Box 8)
    - Eddie "Cleanhead" Vinson (Box 8)
    - Keith Vreeland (Box 8)
    - Junior Walker (Box 8)
    - Sippie Wallace (Box 8)
    - Willie D. Warren (Box 8)
    - Grover Washington, Jr. (Box 8)
    - Muddy Waters (includes Howlin' Wolf and Hound Dog Taylor) (Box 8)
    - Weatherpeople (Box 8)
    - Barb Weinberg 1979 (Box 8)
    - Junior Wells (Box 8)
      (see Buddy Guy and Chicago Blues folders)
    - Kim Weston (Box 8)
    - WGPR-TV, Detroit (Box 8)
    - What If Thinking 1984 (Box 8)
    - Josh White, Jr. (Box 8)
    - Dave Wilborn (Box 9)
    - Jimmy Wilkins Orchestra (Box 9)
    - Joe Willie Wilkins (Box 9)
    - Herbie Williams (Box 9)
    - Jessie Williams (Box 9)
    - Sonny Boy Williamson (Box 9)
    - Howlin' Wolf (Box 9)
      (see also Muddy Waters folder)
    - Stevie Wonder (Box 9)
    - Lyman Woodard (Box 9)
    - Coleman Young (Box 9)
      (see also James Blanchard and Detroit Political folders)
    - Mighty Joe Young (Box 9)
    - Youth Liberation 1973 (Box 9)
    - Buckwheat Zydeco (includes Bill Cosby) (Box 9)
  - Videotape
    - Ten for Two: The John Sinclair Freedom Rally, VHS (Box 9)
  - Motion Pictures
    - Film Reel, Contemporary Jazz Quintet Concert, Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1972 (Reel 1)
      (no sound)
    - Film Reel, Soundtrack to Contemporary Jazz Quintet Concert, Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1972 (Reel 2)
    - Film Reel, end of Contemporary Jazz Quintet Concert, Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1972 (Reel 3)
      (workprint, no sound)
    - Film Reel, Crowd shots, Contemporary Jazz Quintet Concert, Ann Arbor Blues and Jazz Festival 1972 (Reel 4)
  - Realia
    - Wooden sign probably from office of Ann Arbor Sun, painted by Gary Kell (Object 1)
      (sign has image of sun with face and the word "Sun" underneath)
      (separately located)
  - Posters and related oversized visuals
    - Album covers and event posters created through the Bachs' professional ventures (Box 10)
    - Concert posters (Folder UAl)
- Audio Materials
  The Audio Materials series (1995, 0.1 lin. ft.) contains recordings from The UP. "Killer Up!" contains the band's two previously released singles "Just Like an Aborigine" and "Free John Now." The remainder of the music was compiled from previously unreleased recordings. The collection contains a phonograph record and a compact disc of "Killer Up!"
  - The UP, "Killer UP!" released 1995
    (from 1970-1971 original recordings)
    - Compact Disc (Box 4)
      (located in library's CD collection)
    - 10" Phonograph Disc, 33 1/3 rpm stereo (Box 1)
      (located in library's phonograph disc collection)